Inventory of the Department of Mathematics Records 1958-2005
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Department of Mathematics Records 1958-[ongoing] 1958-2005
Special Collections Research Center
00/02/01/22/UA 146
0.60
Dept. of Mathematics arrangement
Administrative Information
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open to all researchers.
Acquisition Information
The materials were acquired by Special Collections Research Center from Various transfers from the Dept. of Mathematics. on 12/22/1987.
Custodial History
This collection was previously part of the University Archives Publications Collection.
Historical Note
Information about this individual or organization may be available in the Special Collections Research Center Wiki: http://scrc.swem.wm.edu/wiki/index.php/Dept. of Mathematics.
Scope and Contents
Acc. 1988.003: Contains syllabi and exams for math courses taught at William and Mary from 1958-1986. The inventory for this accession is available in the box list section of this finding aid.This collection also contains announcements, minutes, reports, and other printed material from the Department of Mathematics.
Additional Information
Index Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
College of William and Mary. Dept. of Mathematics; Faculty--Meetings
Genre/Form of Material:
Announcements; Class materials; Minutes; Reports
Topical Term:
College of William and Mary--Faculty and Staff; Mathematics--Study and teaching--Virginia--History
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Acc. 1988.003, 1958-1986; id55883
  - id55884 (Box 1)
    - Math 101 Exams, 1965-1962; id55894 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Math 103 Syllabus, 1984-1986; id55895 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Math 106 Syllabus, 1983-1986; id55896 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Math 111 Syllabus, 1983-1986; id55897 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Math 112 Syllabus, 1983-1986; id55898 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Math 202 Exams, 1976-1971; id55899 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Math 202 Exams, id55900 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Math 211 Syllabus, 1983-1986; id55901 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Math 212 Syllabus, 1985-1986; id55902 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Math 302 Exams, 1958-1982; id55903 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Math 302 Syllabus, 1985; id55904 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Math 401/501 Syllabus, 1985-1986; id55905 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Math 410 "Outline of Topics Considered", 1961-1978; id55906 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Math 423/523 Syllabus, 1984-1985; id55907 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Math 424/524 Syllabus, 1986; id55908 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Math 504 Exams, 1962-1975; id55909 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Math 570 Syllabus, 1983-1985; id55910 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Math 580 Syllabus, 1985; id55911 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Publications, 1967-2005; id44319
  - id55968 (Box 1)
    - Announcements, 1979-2005; id44320 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Program, 1976-1995; id44321 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1967-1979; id44322 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Self Study, 1972; id44323 (Box 1, Folder 4)